garmentquarter.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Garment Quarter uses and protects any information that you give Garment Quarter when you use this website. Garment Quarter is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Garment Quarter may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## Your rights

The new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) builds on the existing Data Protect act and provides more rights to you:

  * Right to be informed - Customer must easily understand why data is being processed
  * Right of access - Customers can request a copy of information held about them
  * Right to rectification - Customers can request incorrect data to be updated
  * Right to erasure - Customers can request that all data held about them is deleted (provided this is not contravening other legislation)
  * Right to object - Customers have the right to object to direct marketing and processing for purposes of historic research or statistics

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Name
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode
  * Purchase history
  * Information relevant to online surveys

For the list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping including receipts that are needed for returns or exchanges
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * To send promotional emails about new products, promotions, Sales, Garment Quarter events or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Accessing the'privacy dashboard' if you have a registered account with GarmentQuarter.com
  * Opting out of our email newsletters by clicking on the 'unsubscribe' button
  * Contacting [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request your data to be updated or deleted (provided this is not contravening other legislation)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the General Data Protection Regulation. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 25 Penn Street, Bristol Avon BS1 3AU United Kingdom. or email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.  
  
## Who we share your data with

The table below lists the platforms where we share and store your data.

PLATFORM| CATEGORY| WHY?  
---|---|---  
Facebook, Twitter & Instagram | Third Party | Social Sharing, social login and other social media services we offer run by other companies. These companies may drop cookies on your computer when you are using them on our site or if you are already logged in to them.  
Nosto and Dotmailer | Third Party | Nosto provides you with your basket, if you are not ready to purchase your items at the time when you are on your our site. Dotmailer is our email platform in which we send out our newsletters, and any marketing emails.  
Google Analytics | Third Party | Google Analytics uses these cookies to discover when you first visited our site, how often you come back and how long you spend shopping. The information stored by these cookies can be seen only be the relevant teams at Garment Quarter and Google and never shows confidential information, we also use Google Analytics to track the performance of our website.  
Facebook, Instagram, Google & Criteo | Third Party | These partners use Cookies to provide you with personalised adverts when you visit other selected websites. Banner advertising appears on websites which we are affiliated with and we use the information we have learned from cookies to tailor this advertising to things we think you will like, based on your browsing history.  
  
You can opt out of targeted advertising using the links provided below:

Or, unfollow us by heading using the links below:

In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain items of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you.  General information on Klarna you can find [here](https://www.klarna.com/uk/). Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in [Klarna's privacy policy](http://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/Klarna/en_gb/privacy).
